[
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "World Biofuel Day is observed every year on which date?",
        "answer": "10th August",
        "choices": [
            "10th August",
            "8th June",
            "14th Novemeber",
            "16th September"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "When is World Earth Day celebrated",
        "answer": "22nd April",
        "choices": [
            "22nd April",
            "5th June",
            "9th August",
            "2nd October"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "When is World Environment Day celebrated?",
        "answer": "5th June",
        "choices": [
            "5th June",
            "22nd April",
            "9th August",
            "2nd October"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "When is World Sparrow Day celebrated?",
        "answer": "20th March",
        "choices": [
            "20th March",
            "20th May",
            "20th April",
            "20th June"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "Who is considered the founder of ISRO?",
        "answer": "Dr Vikram Sarabhai",
        "choices": [
            "Dr Vikram Sarabhai",
            "Dr Homi Bhabha",
            "DR APJ Abdul Kalam",
            "Dr Satish Dhawan"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "Where is the headquarters of ISRO located?",
        "answer": "Bengaluru",
        "choices": [
            "Bengaluru",
            "Hyderabad",
            "Mumbai",
            "Chennai"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "Name the first President of India",
        "answer": "Rajendra Prasad",
        "choices": [
            "Rajendra Prasad",
            "Savapalli Radhakrishnan",
            "Zakir Hussain",
            "Pratibha Patil"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "Name the first female President of India",
        "answer": "Pratibha Patil",
        "choices": [
            "Pratibha Patil",
            "Draupadi Murmu",
            "Indira Gandhi",
            "Rekha Gupta"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "Name the first President of India belonging to minority religon",
        "answer": "Zakir Hussain",
        "choices": [
            "Zakir Hussain",
            "Draupadi Murmu",
            "Pratibha Patil",
            "Sarvapalli Radhakrishnan"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "Name the first President of India belonging to tribal community",
        "answer": "Draupadi Murmu",
        "choices": [
            "Draupadi Murmu",
            "V V Giri",
            "Rajendra Prasad",
            "Zakir Hussain"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "Name the longest serving president of India till now?",
        "answer": "Rajendra Prasad",
        "choices": [
            "Rajendra Prasad",
            "Savapalli Radhakrishnan",
            "Mohammad Hamid Ansari",
            "Pratibha Patil"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "When is National Space Day celebrated in India?",
        "answer": "23rd August",
        "choices": [
            "23rd August",
            "14th July",
            "26th August",
            "7th Sepetember"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "Which mission's successful landing on the lunar south pole led to the declaration of National Space Day?",
        "answer": "Chandrayaan-3",
        "choices": [
            "Chandrayaan-3",
            "Chandrayaan-2",
            "Chandrayaan-1",
            "Mangalyaan"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "The landing site of the Chandrayaan-3 lander has been named:",
        "answer": "Shiv Shakti Point",
        "choices": [
            "Shiv Shakti Point",
            "Jawahar Point",
            "Mahatma Point",
            "Tiranga Point"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "What was the name of the lander in the Chandrayaan-3 mission?",
        "answer": "Vikram",
        "choices": [
            "Vikram",
            "Pragyan",
            "Agni",
            "Dhruv"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "What is the name of the rover that was deployed from the Chandrayaan-3 lander?",
        "answer": "Pragyan",
        "choices": [
            "Pragyan",
            "Vikram",
            "Agni",
            "Dhruv"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "Which country became the first to successfully land a spacecraft on the lunar south pole?",
        "answer": "India",
        "choices": [
            "India",
            "United States",
            "Russia",
            "China"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "The headquarters of International Court of Justice is situated at",
        "answer": "The Hague, Netherland",
        "choices": [
            "The Hague, Netherland",
            "New York, USA",
            "Geneva, Switzerland",
            "Paris, France"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "Government Report of which of the following countries is known as Yellow Book?",
        "answer": "France",
        "choices": [
            "France",
            "Britain",
            "Italy",
            "Germany"
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "Border Security Force came into existence in",
        "answer": 1965,
        "choices": [
            1965,
            1962,
            1963,
            1964
        ]
    },
    {
        "sheet": "GeneralKnowledge",
        "question": "Montesquieu proposed a division of powers within the government between legislature, executive, and judiciary in which of the following books by him?",
        "answer": "The Spirit of the Laws",
        "choices": [
            "The Spirit of the Laws",
            "My Thoughts",
            "The Republic",
            "The Social Contract"
        ]
    }
]